{
    "subject": "resource/Whitecraigs_railway_station",
    "predicate": "property/original",
    "object": "resource/Lanarkshire_and_Ayrshire_Railway",
    "human_readable": "Whitecraigs railway station was originally part of Lanarkshire and Ayrshire Railway.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9639374613761902,
            "question": "What railway company was Whitecraigs railway station originally part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.84485924243927,
            "question": "Were there any notable events associated with Whitecraigs railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8301097750663757,
            "question": "What is the historical significance of Whitecraigs railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8289756774902344,
            "question": "Were there other railway stations in close proximity to Whitecraigs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7594623565673828,
            "question": "What type of infrastructure was involved in the construction of Whitecraigs railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7290937900543213,
            "question": "What is the current status of the Lanarkshire and Ayrshire Railway?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7212140560150146,
            "question": "Is Whitecraigs railway station still in operation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6192456483840942,
            "question": "To which two counties did the Lanarkshire and Ayrshire Railway connect?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5794075727462769,
            "question": "Has Whitecraigs railway station undergone any major renovations or changes over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5157933831214905,
            "question": "How did the Lanarkshire and Ayrshire Railway impact local communities?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Whitecraigs railway station was originally part of Lanarkshire and Ayrshire Railway.",
            "html": "dbpedia_915_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Whitecraigs railway station undergone any major renovations or changes over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_915_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which two counties did the Lanarkshire and Ayrshire Railway connect?",
            "html": "dbpedia_915_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Whitecraigs railway station still in operation?",
            "html": "dbpedia_915_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_915_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_915_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_915_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_915_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_915_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_915_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_915_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_915_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_915_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_915_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of whether the triple supports the statement:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that:\n\n* Whitecraigs railway station lies on the Neilston branch of the Cathcart Circle Line (document 6)\n* The line was electrified in 1962 and for many years train services were mainly provided by Class 303 \"Blue Train\" electric multiple units, which implies that it was part of a larger railway system (document 6)\n* Whitecraigs station was opened on the former Lanarkshire and Ayrshire Railway (documents 6 and 17)\n\nTherefore, based on this information, it can be concluded that the statement \"Whitecraigs railway station was originally part of Lanarkshire and Ayrshire Railway\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support the statement that Whitecraigs railway station was originally part of the Lanarkshire and Ayrshire Railway. Specifically, both `6.txt` and `17.txt` mention that Whitecraigs station opened on the former Lanarkshire and Ayrshire Railway in 1903."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}